Where am I?
Ow.
These are all bombs?!
No way—
Why is this happening to me?
I'll give you the full rundown.
You have to fight with BIMs, that is, these bombs.
Fight whom, you ask?
Why, the people around you right now.
What's going on?
This is fun!
It's so much fun!
No way.
I'm supposed to play BTOOOM! for real now?
Can I justify killing people as a game?
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
This is where tomorrow brings a new game
It's time to learn that pain is gain
Ready fight
To squash my past despair
kako no shitsubou nuritsubusu tame ni
I've had to sacrifice my future
gisei ni shite kita mirai
Until my life expires
boku no life ga tsukiru made
I'll keep fighting my fate
sono sadame buchikowashiteiku no sa
Ah, break out and start a revolution
Searching for the exact answer
hitotsu no kotae wo sagashite
I challenge myself to an extreme race
genkai no race ni idonde
I know it's my only chance
ichidokiri no chansu to shitte
I'll overcome my preordained fate
seotta unmei koeteikun da yo
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
the game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
Mr. Taira, it's only been two minutes.
That's fine.
I like mine a little crunchy.
Lunchtime!
So damn good!
I can feel it warming me up.
Attack
Delicious!
Was this really for the best?
Sakamoto...
thank you so much.
I was so happy...
when you returned back safely with the food.
Mr. Taira, you've thanked me many times already.
No, I could never say it enough.
I really am grateful.
When I hurt my leg, you risked your life for me.
To me, you're a hero.
Not just anyone could've done that.
Thank you...
Thank you so much!
This man... He's actually crying.
I don't think anyone has ever been this grateful to me in my life.
I'm sure this was the right thing to do.
But why...
Why was I brought to this island?
I'm back!
Yukie, are you here?
Ryouta?
Yukie! What are you doing?!
Hisanobu,
I've... done the worst thing a
parent could ever do.
B-But I had no choice...
Don't talk right now!
I'll go call an ambulance!
I know you got laid off.
You didn't want to worry us,
so you just suffered in silence.
But Ryouta...
Shut the hell up!
You're not even my real dad!
Don't try to act like you are!
Ryouta!
Name: Sakamoto Ryouta
I'm sorry, Hisanobu.
I'm sorry, Ryouta.
I'm just...
so tired.
Wh-What's that?
A c-corpse?
He's really dead.
And he's got no pants.
What's going on?
There could be an enemy at the top of that waterfall.
Let's get out of here, quickly.
W-Wait!
My leg's still hurt.
I can't move that fast.
This time, just leave me here.
Mr. Taira,
don't say something that sad ever again.
There's no way I could leave you behind!
Sakamoto...
I'll go take a look.
You stay here and hide.
Two timers.
Two crackers.
And the three implosions and four crackers I took from the kid.
Probably best not to let Taira know about that yet.
There's someone right ahead.
Should I use my radar?
No, I shouldn't.
Then they'd know that I'm here, too.
It could be a killer.
I need to get as close as I can and see for myself.
That makes two.
Oh, yeah.
I need to hide.
The enemy's close.
Sakamoto...
be careful out there.
Don't throw up...
Don't throw it up!
Food is scarce.
I need every bit to survive!
Swallow it!
It's only been two days since I arrived on this island.
I can't believe how much I've changed in that time.
And that corpse's chip is gone.
Whoever killed him is playing the game.
No choice... I'll use my radar!
Over there?
It must be someone evil, who's killed untold people.
That girl...
We met at the waterfall!
Did she kill him?
Stay away!
A BIM?!
That's the wrong direction.
Could that be a corrosive gas type?
In the game, the gas melts you on contact.
This isn't good!
She lured me out.
She has so many BIMs.
Three... Four players' worth?
Did she take them from other players she's killed?
She looks like a teenage girl, but she must be brutal.
W-Wait!
I don't want to fight,
nor do I have any intentions of participating in this game.
I just want to get off this island alive!
Please put away your BIM, and listen to what I've got to say!
Is she the type who'd listen?
The bad guys are Tyrannos Japan, the people who made the game.
It's stupid to kill each other just because they want us to!
Won't you help me, so we can both get off this island?
If you're not interested, I'll just leave.
Think about it.
I-I guess I convinced her to relax.
Phew.
You tried to get me to drop my guard so you could get close
and do something awful!
Men...
All men are my enemies!
W-Wait!
She's got a terrible throw.
Was that meant to be aimed at me?
But she really did want to kill me.
In that case...
He's too close!
A stun gun?
Blue eyes...
Blonde hair...
Are you a foreigner?
Do you understand me?
I can not speak—
Don't insult me!
I'm Japanese.
I just can't trust men!
Didn't you attack me, too?!
Wait!
You attacked me—
Shut up!
Crap!
It knocked her out?
What's her problem?
Hey, wake up.
Hey...
Honestly.
But this girl...
She smells so nice.
Hey, get it together.
I said, wake up.
All men are my enemies!
I don't want her going nuts again.
I should take away her weapons.
It feels like I'm pulling her panties off.
But...
if I really did,
I bet she wouldn't notice.
She's so cute.
There's no one around.
That was close...
What was I thinking?
And he's got no pants.
What's going on?
Oh! Here on the island, this girl...
She was attacked by that man.
I want... I want... I want you!
You're awake?
You got hit with your own stun gun.
You'll be too numb to move for a while.
Don't worry.
I won't hurt you.
I'll take you somewhere safe.
A timer BIM?
She had one hidden?!
Don't do it! Don't be stupid!
I won't let you... rape me...
I'd rather die.
All guys are just animals!
If I'm going to wind up raped and then murdered,
I'd rather just kill myself!
Die while I'm still pure...
I've got nowhere to go back to, anyway!
I don't care if I die.
I don't care.
This girl...
She really was going to kill herself.
It wasn't a bluff.
Just now, she actually was going to throw away her life.
Drink up.
It's warm coffee.
Mr. Taira, that's...
We've got no cups; what else could I use?
It's as good a cup as any.
I washed it out, so don't worry.
Here.
You must've been through a lot.
But worry no more!
You've got us with you now!
We won't do anything weird.
I promise! Scouts honor!
I decided that I'd make it off this island on my own, without playing the game.
So, if you could, I'd really like you to help us.
Let's escape together.
Thankfully, we've got enough food to last a while.
Lots of bombs, too. So there's nothing to be afraid of.
No.
Even if we get back,
there's no guarantee anything will be waiting for us.
What do you mean?
People who knew each of us well picked us to be sent here.
They selected us as someone they wanted to disappear.
So even if we went back to those people, what then?
What do you mean?!
You mean our friends and families have abandoned us?
I can't believe that!
I have a great relationship with my family.
They wouldn't want me to disappear!
I just meant that they're people we know.
Recently, have you done anything to someone that would make them hate you?
C-Come to think of it...
I got in a big fight with a customer last month.
How do you know about this?
We weren't told anything about this!
Where did you hear it?
Where?
They told me.
We all picked you.
I hope you disappear!
Someone picked us to disappear?
Then, that would go for everyone on this island?
Taira?
That kid?
Me, too?
Someone chose me.
No way.
That can't be...
It can't...
My mom?
I don't have anywhere else to go.
I don't have anywhere...
What are you saying?!
You can't say that!
You've got to live!
We need to survive and escape this island...
to get back home!
Once we're back, we can work things out!
We can't give up!
What's wrong?
There's something out there.
I-Is someone nearby?
I heard something!
Nothing?
But I can hear something getting closer.
Radar canceling?
But...
Wh-What are those?!
They aren't human...
Panthers?
Wolves?
There should've been a radar response!
Fire! More fire!
Get away from the forest!
What are you doing? Come on!
That's right.
That hit from the stun gun!
Come on! Stand up! Hurry!
Th-These things are...
giant lizards!
You've gotta be kidding!
We lost each other that day
ano hi kara katamuita
You're in another time and space
jikan jikuu no dokoka ni kimi wa ite
Even if I reach out my fingers
doko made mo yubi no saki
I can only feel the breeze
nobashita kedo kaze shika tsukamenai
Day and night, I feel so guilty
asa mo yoru mo kokoro ga
For the wrong choices I've made
semeru no yo naze doushite
Now I just need some
ato sukoshi jibun sae
Trust in myself
shinjitara
Can't go away
can't go away
I'm cowering away again
dame da to mata nigeteru
I need to face reality
mitsumerunda riaru wo
I was kind to my family,
but I was a monster at work.
It wouldn't surprise me if any of them hated me.
This is karma.
Yes, this is my punishment.
Episode
Night
of Sacrifice